
const QuizData = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: ` Who invented Pokémon games ?`,
      options: [`Yoshiro Nakamatsu`, `Satoshi Taijiri`, `Momofuku Ando`, `Tomohiro Nishikado`],
      answer: `Satoshi Taijiri`
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `How many Pokémon are in the 1st generation?`,
      options: [`151`, `250`, `30`, `300`],
      answer: `151`
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `what's the meaning of Pokémon?`,
      options: [`Small monster`, `Capsules Monster`, `Poket Monsters`, `Catching insects`],
      answer: `Poket Monsters`
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `Pokémon is distributed by?`,
      options: [`Sony`, `Microsoft`, `Nintendo`,`Sega`],
      answer: `Nintendo`
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: `When was Pokémon first releaased?`,
      options: [`June 30 1990`, `Septembre 15 2000`, `March 1 1988`, `Febuary 27 1996`],
      answer: `Febuary 27 1996`
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: `Which one is the first Pokémon games versions`,
      options: [`Red & Green`, `Silver & Gold`, `Ruby et Saphire`, `Diamond & Pearl`],
      answer: `Red & Green`
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: `How many type of Pokémon was created?`,
      options: [`34`, `10`, `15`, `18`],
      answer: `18`
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: `With what can we catch Pokémons?`,
      options: [`Pokéball`, `Pokébag`, `Pokétrap`,`Pokéfood`],
      answer: `Pokéball`
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: `How many Pokémon's generation were published?`,
      options: [`4`, `9`, `8`, `6`],
      answer: `8`
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: `Who illustrated the original artwork for Pokémon games?`,
      options: [`Ed Tsuwaki`, `Hayao Miyazaki`, `Hirosuke Ueno`, `Ken Sugimori`],
      answer: `Ken Sugimori`
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: `What kind of game is Pokémon?`,
      options: [`Role playing`, `Virtual reality`, `simultation`, `Adventure`],
      answer: `Role playing`
    }
  ];

  export default QuizData